(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
みんな!
Everyone!
速報だよ!!
Breaking news!!
何? 何? 何?
What? What? What?
なんと 一番くじ
Actually, an Ichiban Kuji...
hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSSの
for hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS...
発売が決定したんだって!!
has been scheduled for release!!
ReGLOSSが一番くじ?
ReGLOSS is an Ichiban Kuji?
ドッキリか何か?
Is this a prank or something?
えー でもどんなラインナップなんだろう?
Eh, I wonder what the lineup is like.
みんな!
Everyone!
運試ししてみてね!
Try your luck!
なんと 11月13日
Actually, starting November 13th...
木曜日より順次発売予定のなんだって
...Thursday, it's scheduled to be released sequentially.
ぜひみんなチャレンジしてみてね!
Please everyone give it a try!
なんと 出来立てホヤホヤの
Actually, we have freshly made...
サンプルをスタジオへご用意いただいております!
...samples ready in the studio!
でも おまえらにはまだ見せられないよ〜
But we can't show them to you guys yet~
ないないよ〜
Nope, nope~
でも ちょっとだけ
But, just a little bit...
教えちゃおっかな〜
...maybe I'll tell you~
まずは 描きおろしイラストを使った
First, using newly drawn illustrations...
ビジュアルボードがあったよね!
...there's a visual board, right!
しかも イラストの背景にそれぞれにマッチした
And, matching each illustration background...
モチーフがいろいろ入ってたよね〜
...there were various motifs!
はじめ 「押忍!」って書いてあった!
Hajime had "Osu!" written on it!
ちょこのっこフィギュア!
Chokonokko figures!
ホロライブ一番くじではおなじみのやつもあったね
Those familiar ones from hololive Ichiban Kuji were there too.
表情がとっても可愛かった!
The expressions were very cute!
なんかお出かけする時とかにさ
Like when you go out...
バッグに忍ばせて一緒に連れて行ってほしくない?
...don't you want to tuck them in your bag and take them along?
髪の毛のね この塗り分けとか
The hair color separation...
グラデーションとかも すごい小さいのに綺麗なんだよ〜!
...and gradation are really beautiful despite being so small!
ラストワン賞っぽい奴は なんかこう デカかったね!
The one that looks like the Last One prize was... big!
抱きしめて...眠れる。
You could hug it and... sleep.
ヒントは以上です!
That's all for the hints!
気になる詳細は 9月16日に一番くじホームページでも公開予定!
Details will be released on the Ichiban Kuji homepage on September 16!
お楽しみにー!
Look forward to it!
なんと お知らせはこれだけじゃない!
Actually, that's not all the news!
2025年9月の第4週より
Starting from the 4th week of September 2025...
順次全国のカプセル自販機にて
...sequentially at capsule toy machines nationwide...
いよいよ ReGLOSSの...
...finally, ReGLOSS...
ガシャポン商品！
Gachapon products!
2025年9月第4週より順次発売予定！
Scheduled for release starting from the 4th week of September 2025!
ホロライブデバイス リグロス ミニCDコレクションが販売開始となります！
hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS Mini CD Collection is now on sale!
イェーイ！イェーイ！
Yay! Yay!
こちら小さなCDのようなチャームで...
This is a charm like a small CD...
...CD風プレートやジャケットカードも取り出せる仕様になってます。
...and it's designed so you can take out the CD-style plate and jacket card.
すごーい！かわいいー！
Amazing! So cute!
ラインナップはデビュー曲「瞬間ハートビート」から...
The lineup includes everything from our debut song "Shunkan Heartbeat"...
...1st Album『ReGLOSS』など、シークレットを含む全6種！
...to our 1st album "ReGLOSS", for a total of 6 types including a secret one!
どれが出るかはカプセルを開けてのお楽しみ〜！
Open the capsule to see which one you get~!
ガシャポンオフィシャルサイトで売っているお店を検索することもできるので、ぜひ参考にしてください！
You can also search for stores that sell them on the Gachapon official website, so please check it out!
ということで、一番くじもガシャポンもよろしくねー！
So, please look forward to both the Ichibankuji and Gachapon!
お願いしまーす！ガシャポンしに行こうぜ〜！
Please! Let's go do some Gachapon~!
行く行く〜！
Let's go, let's go~!
Reach the top! We are ReGLOSS!
このあとはReGLOSS 2周年記念配信！
Next up is the ReGLOSS 2nd Anniversary commemorative stream!
いったい何が起こるんだ！？
Just what is going to happen!?
たのしみ〜
Exciting~
でも配信の前に！ReGLOSSの2周年に関するたくさんのお知らせを...
But before the stream! Let's look back on all the many announcements...
...みんなで振り返っちゃいまーす！
...regarding ReGLOSS's 2nd anniversary all together!
イェーイ！じゃあまずは記念グッズ！
Yay! First, the commemorative goods!
ReGLOSS 2周年を記念したグッズがホロライブオフィシャルショップと...
Goods commemorating ReGLOSS's 2nd anniversary are now on sale at the hololive official shop...
...全国のHMVとHMV&BOOKSの店舗で販売中です！
...and HMV/HMV&BOOKS stores nationwide!
ラインナップはこちら！
Here is the lineup!
2025.9.12 販売開始予定！
Sale scheduled to begin on September 12, 2025!
おおー！いいね！いっぱいある！
Ooh! Nice! There's so many!
カナデのとかめっちゃかわいい！
Kanade's one is so cute!
ね、かわいい！R ReGLOSSだね。Rですよ。トートバッグいいね！
Right, cute! It's R-ReGLOSS. It's an R. The tote bag is nice!
ね、おしゃれ！チェキ全部飾りたいね！
Yeah, stylish! I want to display all the cheki!
わかる！素敵！
I know! Wonderful!
ランダム缶バッジはHMV限定商品になっているので...
The random tin badges are HMV exclusive items...
...ぜひ全国のHMVとHMV&BOOKSにお越しください！
...so please visit HMV and HMV&BOOKS stores nationwide!
お願いします！
Please!
そんなHMVとHMV&BOOKSで本日から開催中の...
We'll also recap the fair being held at HMV and HMV&BOOKS starting today...
ReGLOSS 2nd Anniversary フェア
ReGLOSS 2nd Anniversary Fair
「ReGLOSS 2nd Anniversaryフェア」についてもおさらいです！
the "ReGLOSS 2nd Anniversary Fair"!
今回のフェアではホロライブグッズを税込2,200円お買い上げごとに...
In this fair, for every 2,200 yen (tax included) spent on hololive goods...
2025.9.13(土)〜2025.10.5(日)
September 13, 2025 (Sat) - October 5, 2025 (Sun)
...限定クリアカードをランダムで1枚プレゼントしちゃいます！
...you'll receive one random limited edition clear card!
フェアは10月5日まで。みんな楽しんでね！
The fair runs until October 5th. Everyone, please enjoy!
そして2周年記念のボイスも販売中です！
And the 2nd anniversary commemorative voices are also on sale!
今回は「旅」をコンセプトにしたボイスで...
This time, the voices are themed around "travel"...
...シチュエーションボイスと掛け合いボイスドラマの2種類があります！
...and there are two types: situation voices and a dialogue voice drama!
これなんと旅行の準備をしてる様子であったりとか、あとは移動中の様子なんかを...
These voices allow you to experience things like preparing for a trip or being in transit...
...ReGLOSSと一緒に旅のワクワクを味わえること間違いなしのボイスとなっております。
...so you'll definitely get to experience the excitement of traveling with ReGLOSS.
ぜひ何度でも聴いて楽しんでください！
Please listen to them over and over and enjoy!
たのしみ〜
Exciting~
いやまさからでんちゃんがな、旅行前にあんなことするなんて...
I can't believe Raden-chan would do something like that before a trip...
確かにな。ちょっとね。
True. A little bit.
柄にないことしちゃったな。だよね。
I did something out of character. Right.
はい、ということでReGLOSSの2周年は超・超・超盛り沢山！！
Yes, so ReGLOSS's 2nd anniversary is super, super, super packed!!
GLOSSERもそうでない人も皆さんで盛り上がっちゃいましょう〜！
Glossers and non-Glossers alike, let's all get excited together!
イェーイ！
Yay!
このあとの2周年記念配信でもなにかだ、特大の発表があるとか！？
And apparently there's some kind of huge announcement in the 2nd anniversary stream coming up!?
さあ。
Well.
え、心当たりが無さすぎる...
Eh, I have no idea...
いや心当たりあって！？
Hey, have an idea!?
すんごい特大のアレだよアレ。どこどこ！？
It's that really huge thing. Where, where!?
皆最後まで絶対に見逃さないようにしてね！
Everyone, make sure you don't miss it until the very end!
それでは配信スタートまでもう少々お待ちくださーい！
Then, please wait a little longer until the stream starts!
せーの！ReGLOSSでした〜！！！バイバイ！
Ready! We were ReGLOSS~!!! Bye bye!
2025.09.13(SAT) 20:00 START ReGLOSS ch
Starts on September 13, 2025 (Sat) at 20:00 on the ReGLOSS channel
うわっ! 巨大なソーセージが!
Uwaa! A giant sausage!
巨大なソーセージが襲ってくる!
A giant sausage is attacking me!
にゃんにゃん
Nyan-nyan
みんな気をつけて!
Everyone, watch out!
なんかめっちゃいびきうるさいんだけど
Man, someone's snoring is really loud.
やばいこれ!
This is bad!
なでちゃん?
Nade-chan?
なんか食べちゃいけない逆流...
Like, don't eat the reverse...
なで...
Nade...
そんなほうじ茶の海なんて...
A sea of roasted green tea...
うっ、泳げないよ...
Ugh, I can't swim in that...
待って、気をつけてね、なんか...
Wait, watch out, there's something...
うわっ! 今目の前に...
Whoa! Right in front of me...
「後ろを振り返ってはいけない」
"Do not look back"
「席を立ってはいけない」って書いてある
and "Do not stand up from your seat."
這いちゃうわよ私!
I'm gonna end up crawling!
もしかしたら振り返ったら死ぬのかも!
Maybe we'll die if we look back!
試してみようぜ!
Let's try it out!
やばいやばいやばい!
Oh no, no, no!
じゃあ、奏試してみて!
Okay, Kanade, you try it!
これ、まだ夢か? 夢っぽいな、これまだ。
Is this still a dream? It still feels like one.
夢じゃないのかな、これ... らでちゃん。
Is it not a dream... Raden-chan?
夢じゃないよ!
It's not a dream!
お、ていうか、あ、なんか出てきたよ!
Oh, wait, something just appeared!
はいよ。
Here.
何?
What?
えっと、読み上げるね。
Let me read it out.
聞こえますか... ReGLOSSのみなさん...
Can you hear me... members of ReGLOSS?
私はこの部屋に封印されたお宝...
I am the treasure sealed in this room...
今... あなたたちの心に直接呼びかけています...
Now... I am calling directly to your hearts...
なんだって?
Say what?
今から、あなたたちに2年目最後の試練を与えます...
I will now give you the final trial of your second year...
試練!
A trial!
みなさんで謎を解いて、3年目への扉を開けてください。
Solve the mystery together and open the door to the third year.
はい。
Okay.
謎解きのルールは簡単です...
The rules for this puzzle are simple...
4文字のキーワードを見つけ出すのです。
You must find a four-letter keyword.
おお。
Oh.
ただし、席を立ってはいけません...
However, you must not stand up from your seat...
真後ろだ...
Directly behind...
真後ろだけは、振り向いてもいけません...
and you must not look directly behind you.
えー...
Oh...
ルールはそれだけです。
Those are all the rules.
ふむふむふむ。
I see, I see.
キーワードがわかったら、一人ずつ順番に読み上げてください...
Once you know the keyword, please read it out in order...
みなさんの絆なら、必ずクリアできるでしょう...
With your bonds, you'll surely be able to clear it...
ほう。
Ho.
それでは、開始です。
Now, let us begin.
さあ、みなさんで3年目の扉を開けるのです!
Go forth and open the door to the third year together!
もう3年目始まってるんですけど!
The third year has already started, though!
このまま扉を開けるもなにも...
Forget opening the door, we're already here...
まだ開けられてなかったってこと?
Does it mean it wasn't officially open yet?
なるほど。
I see.
じゃあ、とりあえずなんか目の前にさぁ。
Well, for now, there's something in front of us...
お、なんかあるね。これ何だ?
Oh, look, there's something. What is this?
なんかある。
There's something.
パズルっぽいのが。
Looks like a puzzle.
クロスワードっぽい!
Looks like a crossword!
ちょ、クロスワードっぽい奴が置いてない?
Hey, isn't there a crossword-like thing here?
あ、本当だ!
Oh, you're right!
なだろう。あんこ?
I wonder what it is. Anko?
あんこ?
Anko?
いや違うこれ、なんかあのバラバラになったひらがな読んだだけだから、これ何も関係ない奴ね。
No, I just read the scattered hiragana, so it's probably unrelated.
えっ、これ「だー!」
Wait, this is "Daaa!"
はじめは「いーいんぐ」。
Hajime's is "Eee-ing".
いんぐ?
Ing?
いんぐ。え、それさぁ、あれでしょ? その問題じゃなくてさぁ、あのクロスワードの埋まってる部分だけ読んでるでしょ!
Ing. Hey, you're just reading the filled-in parts of the crossword, not the actual clue!
そう、そう、そう。
Right, right, right.
えっ、じゃあ、ちょっと一旦リリカの横のカギの1番言うね。
Okay, let me read my horizontal clue number 1 first.
ある飲み物を作るとき、
When making a certain drink,
精米歩合を50%以上60%以下で作るとこう呼ばれる。
it is called this if the rice polishing ratio is between 50% and 60%.
あ! これ、吟醸じゃない?
Oh! Isn't this "Ginjo"?
奏さん、ごめん、1ミリも聞いてなかった。ごめん、ごめん。
Kanade-san, sorry, I didn't listen to a single word. My bad.
なんっで! ごめん! ごめん!
Why not! Sorry! Sorry!
ある飲み物を作るとき、
When making a certain drink,
精米歩合を50%以上60%以下で作るとこう呼ばれる。
it's called this if the rice polishing ratio is between 50% and 60%.
純米? 純米吟醸?
Junmai? Junmai Ginjo?
え、でも「ぎ」から始まる言葉で
Well, it starts with "Gi"
「う」で終わるのだから、吟醸じゃないかなって思ったんだけど。
and ends with "U", so I thought maybe "Ginjo".
え、博識! そうなの?
Wow, you're so knowledgeable! Is that right?
えっ、すごーい!
Whoa, amazing!
え、違うかなぁ。
Or maybe I'm wrong.
え、わかんない。
I don't know.
わかんない。でも「ぎ」から始まって「う」で終わる言葉他に知らないから、それでいいんじゃない?
I don't know either, but since I don't know any other word starting with "Gi" and ending with "U", that should be it.
いいじゃん、いいじゃん! 書いていいよ!
That works! Just go ahead and write it in!
書いていいよ!
Go ahead!
じゃあ次、らでんちゃんなんかある?
Next, Raden-chan, do you have anything?
えっと、えっと、えっとねぇ... えっと... あぁ...
Uh... well... let's see... uh...
ちょっと待って今、あの、問題が、来てる問題がガチすぎて、
Wait a minute. This question I got is just way too serious.
ちょっと今頭が真っ白になった。ちょっと別の人、別の人!
My mind just went completely blank. Ask someone else first!
あ、じゃあ奏どうかな?
Ah, then how about Kanade?
えっと、まる1の横が...
Well, horizontal number 1 is...
こいつはタンギング。短かだけど、奥深い。
This is tonguing. Short but deep.
あぁ、タンギング?
Oh, tonguing?
リコーダーでなんかタンギングだと、「と、と、と」とかじゃないのかなぁ。
If it's tonguing on a recorder, wouldn't it be "tu, tu, tu" or something?
やばい、全然わかんない!
Oh no, I have no idea at all!
タ、タ、タンギング。タチツテトなのかな。
Ta-ta-tonguing. Is it "Ta-Chi-Tsu-Te-To"?
かな?
Maybe?
短かだけど、奥深い。
Short but deep.
わかった。いいこと考えた。一旦、みんな自分の文章、自分の問題読んで、
I've got it. I have a good idea. For now, everyone read your own questions,
わかるやつは埋めよう。で、わかんないやつを相談する形にしよう。
and fill in the ones you know. Then we can consult on the ones we don't.
わかった! そうだね。
Got it! Good idea.
そうじゃないとあんまり時間がなくなる気がしちゃうから。
Otherwise, I feel like we'll run out of time.
わかった。時間とかあるのかよくわかんないけど。
Okay. Not sure if there is a time limit, but...
え? あはっ、これわかるよ!
Eh? Oh! I know this one!
え?
Eh?
これ、まる4はわかればいいってこと?
Does it mean I just need to figure out number 4?
おにょじょって、エモくなりがちな...
Like... becoming "emo"...
料理の味加減?
the seasoning/flavor of cooking?
わかんない。なんか優しいな。
I don't know, that sounds kind of gentle.
え、奏わかったよ!
Oh, Kanade figured it out!
お、全部わかった?
Oh! You figured out everything?
いや、全部わかんないけど、まる4がわかるから、なんかキーワードナンバー3がわかりました。
No, not everything, but since I know number 4, I've figured out keyword number 3!
おお!
Oh!
これでいいの?
Is this okay?
えー、キーワードナンバー3はじゃあ、なんだったかな？奏。
Keyword number 3... what was it again? Kanade.
キーワード… えっと、丸4が「まぜまぜして食べる料理。お好みでコチュジャンをかけて」って書いてあったから…
Keyword... um, number 4 said "a dish you mix together. Add gochujang to your liking," so...
ビビンバで。
it's Bibimbap.
あー、確かに。
Ah, true.
その最後のワードの「バ」でした。
So it was the last letter, "ba".
バか！
Ba!
バ、バ、バって何だ？
Ba, ba... What's "ba"?
何？バ？
What? Ba?
バか、何も無いじゃん。
Ba? There's nothing.
まあ、じゃあ「バ」ね。
Well, "ba" then.
え、ごめん、リリカ、どっちも分かんなくて。
Um, sorry Ririka, I don't get either of them.
何？
What?
あの、4番目。物事の具合を上手く処理すること。
Um, the 4th one. "Handling the state of things well."
料理の味加減についても言うっていうのが…
Also used for the seasoning of food...
ごめん、料理関係は本当に分かんない。
Sorry, I really don't know anything about cooking.
えー！料理系Vtuberじゃなかったのー！？
Whaaat?! I thought you were a cooking Vtuber?!
もう引退した方がいいかも、料理系。
You might want to retire from being a cooking one.
「物事の具合を上手く処理すること」って何？
What's "handling the state of things well"?
…しんちょーりつ？
...Progress rate?
ほー。
Oho.
でも「味加減」のことそう言うかな？
But would you say that for "seasoning"?
味加減…
Seasoning...
調整？
Adjusting?
スタ、ベロ…
Sta, tongue...
何かダサいのがあった。
There was something lame.
味、味、んー。
Taste, taste, hmm.
これさ、振り返っちゃいけないんだよね。
We aren't allowed to look back, right?
駄目だよ。
You can't.
このさ、イラスト何なの？
What is this illustration?
え、どこまでさ、振り返っていいの？
Um, how far can I turn around?
どこまで見ていいもんなの？
How much can I see?
「真後ろ見た時だけ」って言ってた。
They said "only when looking directly behind".
横は大丈夫なはず。
Sides should be fine.
じゃあ、ここは見れる。
So I can see here.
横はいいんだ。
Sides are okay.
横… え、リリカ？
Sides... Um, Ririka?
はい。
Yes.
奏側の横に何か無い？
Is there anything on Kanade's side?
奏側の横に…
On Kanade's side...
え、何か人を殺せそうなバットが置いてある。
Wait, there's a bat that looks like it could kill someone.
バット！？
A bat?!
あとリコーダーもある。
And a recorder too.
バットとリコーダー！？
A bat and a recorder?!
バットでいいんだね、それは。
So it's really a bat.
え、何かトゲトゲしたバット。
Um, a spiked bat.
何か本当に、あの、鬼の金棒みたいな感じ。
It's really like, an ogre's club.
鬼の金棒！？
An ogre's club?!
うん。
Yeah.
なるほど。ありがと。
I see. Thanks.
自分の位置からだと見えても、な…
Even if I can see it from where I am...
あ、次の番だ。
Oh, it's the next turn.
へー、どう？
Hmm, how's it going?
何も分からないじゃん。
I don't understand anything.
何か分からないのあった？
Was there something you didn't get?
え、何これ。
Um, what's this?
「アーモンドのような香りがする危険な薬品。シアン化カリウム、またの名を何？」
"A dangerous chemical that smells like almonds. Potassium cyanide, also known as what?"
えー、むずい。
Whoa, that's hard.
危険じゃん。
That's dangerous.
滑舌が何て言ったか今分かんなかった。
I didn't catch what you said with that stuttering.
え、アーモンドみたいな香りがする危険な薬品、シアン化カリウム。
A dangerous chemical that smells like almonds, potassium cyanide.
またの名は何？
What's its other name?
青酸カリとかじゃないの？
Isn't it Seisan Kari?
危険な薬品って。
Since it's a dangerous chemical.
それか！
That's it!
来た！ジーニアスやん！
There we go! You're a genius!
青酸カリか。
Seisan Kari, huh.
文字数合ってる。
The number of characters matches.
おー、すごい！
Oh, amazing!
ありがちゅん。
Thanks-chun.
オッケー。
Okay.
行こう。
Let's go.
え？
Eh?
あとは何だ？
What's left?
あ、はい、はい、はい。
Ah, okay, okay.
分かっちゃった。
I got it.
え、リリカのヒントが…
Um, Ririka's hint says...
反対側の椅子の背中に書かれている文字が入るってなってて。
it says "a letter written on the back of the opposite chair goes here."
多分リリカの反対が番長なんだよね。
And Hajime's probably the one opposite Ririka.
だかららでんちゃんか奏かどっちか、番長の背中見れない？
So can Raden or Kanade see the back of Hajime's chair?
あ、らでん見ます。
Oh, I'll look.
「ん」って書いてあるよ。
It says "n".
ん？
N?
んか。
N, then.
ってことは、料理の味加減のやつが、2文字目が「ん」なんだけど、それで4文字。
That means the seasoning one has "n" as the second letter, and it's 4 letters long.
味加減。味加減。
Seasoning. Seasoning.
料理の味加減についても言うし…
It's used for food seasoning...
物事の具合を上手く処理すること。
and also for "handling the state of things well."
盤面処理とか…
Board clear...
お、駄目だ。カードゲームの名前しか出てこない。
Oh, no. Only card game terms are coming to mind.
4文字。
4 letters.
ん、ん、ん、ん。
N, n, n, n.
ん、ん、ん、ん、だよね。
It's n, n, n, n, right.
感覚。
Intuition?
Sense?
あ、分かったかも。
Ah, I might have it.
え？
Eh?
塩梅！
Anbai!
あー、そうかも！
Ah, that could be it!
え、すごい！
Wow, amazing!
そうかも。分かんないけど。
Maybe. I don't know though.
だと、リリカの最初のキーワードは「あ」かも。
If so, Ririka's first keyword might be "A".
おー。
Oh.
あ、
A,
ん、
n,
ば…
ba...
え？何それ？
Eh? What's that?
このキーワードね。並べた時に。
This keyword. When you line them up.
番長は、あと何が分かってない？
Hajime, what else do you not know?
えーっと、4番だけ分かってないんだけど…
Um, I only don't know the 4th one...
ヒントは反対側の椅子の背中だから、リリカの背中。
The hint is the back of the opposite chair, so Ririka's.
問題は？
What's the question?
ストリートダンス、クランプでの特徴的な振り付け。
A characteristic move in street dance/krump.
ストンプ、チェストポップ、あと一つは？
Stomp, chest pop, and what's the last one?
何だろう。リリカの背中を見てあげて。
What could it be. Check the back of Ririka's chair.
おい！誰も見ねえのかよ！
Hey! Is nobody going to look?!
見てる見てる！
We're looking!
奏が見れないよ。
Kanade can't see it.
待って、リリカの背中見たらいいんだね。
Wait, so I just need to see the back of Ririka's chair.
はい。「す」。
Okay. "Su".
「す」が入る、ダンスのやつ？
Dance move that starts with "su"?
ストリップ？
Strip?
それは如月こちょ。分かんない。
That's Kisaragi Kocho. I don't know.
ステップ。
Step.
スク…
Sku...
すー、すー、すみません。
Su-, su-, sumimasen.
すみません。
I'm sorry.
全然分かんないな。
I have no idea.
すみません、ちょっとぶった斬ってしまって申し訳ないんですが。
Sorry, I hate to cut you off.
らでんのも行こう。
Let's do Raden's too.
誰か、私の背中に書かれている文字を読んで欲しいです。
I want someone to read the letter written on my back.
はい。
Okay.
「び」です。
It's "bi".
び？
Bi?
うん。バビブベボの「び」。
Yeah. The "bi" in "ba-bi-bu-be-bo".
そう。オッケー。
Right. Okay.
どんな問題？
What's the question?
えっとね、江戸時代に…
Um, in the Edo period...
江戸時代に小袖の色として流行した青色の名前、宝石ラピスラズリの和名やガラスの昔の呼び方が含まれて...
The name of the blue color popular for sleeves in the Edo period, including the Japanese name for lapis lazuli and the old name for glass...
ガチすぎだろこれ！
This is too serious!
問題が難しすぎて一瞬で頭パーンってなっちゃった、最初。
The questions were so hard that my brain just went pop at first.
「び」が入ってるんだ。
It has 'bi' in it.
こか、しゅなのかな。
Is it 'ko' or 'shu'?
美白とか、びこ...こはく？
Bihaku or... biko... kohaku?
最初の一文字が「こ」なんだよね。こび...
The first character is 'ko', right? Kobi...
ふむふむ。
I see, I see.
へぇー。
Heh.
こび...かびり...こび...こびり...
Kobi... kabiri... kobi... kobiri...
やばい、あと10分しかないんだけど。
Wait, there's only 10 minutes left.
えー分かんないよー。
I don't get it!
やばいよー。こび...
This is bad. Kobi...
コバルトブルー！
Cobalt Blue!
違う。あー、でも多分これかな？
No. Ah, but maybe this is it?
何？番長なんかあった？
What? Did you find something, Bancho?
え、なんか「しょにょ...」あ、インクってなるんだけど、しゅが入るって言ってたじゃん。
Wait, it's like 'shonyo...', ah, 'ink', but you said 'shu' is in it.
で、アームスウィングかなみたいな。
So I thought maybe it's 'arm swing'.
おおー！
Ohh!
でも分からん、そんな言葉知らんからな。
But I don't know, I don't know that word.
生み出しちゃった、言葉を。
I just invented a word.
生み出しちゃったかー。
You invented it, huh?
いいじゃん。他に番長から連ちゃんで何かヒントになりそうなものない？
That's fine. Anything else from you that could be a hint?
この一文字、この問題解ければいけるかもなみたいな。
If we solve this one character, this problem might be solved.
えーともう4番だけだな。
Well, there's only number 4 left.
せっ...リリナネデ、リリナネデの間にあるのは、トゲトゲのバットだったんだよね。
Se... in between 'Ririnanede' was a spiked bat.
トゲトゲのバットとリコーダー。
A spiked bat and a recorder.
そう、トゲトゲのバットってさ、なんかトゲトゲのバット以外の言い方ってない？
Yeah, is there any other way to say 'spiked bat'?
金棒。
Iron club.
金棒。あ、間が二文字目に「ん」が来る。
Iron club. Ah, an 'n' comes in the second character.
「ん」が来る！
An 'n' comes!
棍棒じゃない？
Isn't it 'club'?
ああー！それじゃない？
Ahh! That's it, isn't it?
棍棒って言うよね。
It is called a club.
待って、ちょっと待って。最初の問題、自分で書いて間違ってる説ある。
Wait, hold on. I might have written the first question wrong myself.
え、ちょっと待って。それなぞとこ。
Wait, what? Let's solve that mystery.
この色で写真を加工するとエモくなり勝ち...
Editing photos with this color makes them look emo...
セピア。
Sepia.
だよね、合ってるよね。
Right? That's correct.
え、何何、全部読んでみて。
What? Read the whole thing.
え、元々はイカスミのことであった。
Originally, it meant squid ink.
モノトーンとかモノクロ？
Monotone or monochrome?
いや、でもセピア。あ、多分...
No, it's sepia. Oh, maybe...
セピアだと思って。しかも青酸カリにも繋がるし。
I thought it was sepia. And it connects to cyanide too.
で、あのパーティー会場で使うハンマーの...
And the hammer used at party venues...
ピコピコハンマー。
Toy hammer.
って埋まってるんだ。
Is filled in.
でそのダンスのやつだけ分かんないんだ。
And I just don't know the dance one.
そう。で「ア」から始まって「シュ」が付くんだったら、まぁスウィングにはなるだろうなっていうので。
Right. If it starts with 'A' and ends in 'shu', it's probably swing.
「あ」、一文字、「ん」。
'A', one character, 'n'.
まぁ「あ」で、あと一文字だったら腕かなみたいな。
Well, with 'A' and one character, I thought maybe it's 'ude' (arm).
ほうほうほう。
I see, I see.
アームってこと？
You mean 'arm'?
で、それで番長のワードは何になるの？
So then what does your word become?
キーワードは「ム」になる。
The keyword becomes 'mu'.
なるほど。
I see.
あ、ば、むってこと？
So 'a', 'ba', 'mu'?
じゃアルバムじゃねえかよ！
Then it's 'album'!
逆に考えようぜ、らでんちゃん。
Let's think backward, Raden-chan.
「あ、ば、む」の中で、ん、の中に入る言葉何かあるかな？
In 'a, ba, mu', is there any word that fits in the middle?
あじばむとか？
Like 'ajibamu'?
あしばむ。
Ashibamu.
あせばむ。
Asebamu (Sweaty).
ああ、いい、あせばむ、いいなそれ。
Ah, nice, asebamu is good.
キーワードナンバー2なんですけど、
For keyword number 2,
「る」のような気がしています。
I feel like it's 'ru'.
いやもうその話してるでしょ！
Wait, we're already talking about that!
いやー、なんかあれだな、難しく考えすぎたんだな、きっと。
Man, I guess I was overthinking it.
もういいかもしんない。
It might be fine now.
あ、じゃ特にそのラピス・ラズリの和名が分かったとかじゃなくて、なんとなく「る」な気がすると？
So it's not that you figured out the Japanese name for lapis lazuli, you just feel like it's 'ru'?
多分ね「こびるり」のような気がするんだけど、らでん側にすごい問題が起きていて。
I think it's 'kobiruri', but there's a big problem on Raden's side.
何が問題かって言うと、らでんの周りに色々ヒントがあるのは、なんとなく分かってるんだけど、
The problem is, I know there are various hints around Raden, but
目が悪すぎてさ、何を表してるのか全く分からん。
my eyesight is so bad I have no idea what they represent.
らでんちゃんの隣にはピストルがあるよ。
There's a pistol next to Raden-chan.
ピストルね、あと何かもいっこない？
A pistol, okay. Anything else?
絵画っぽいんだけど、なんかお股なのか羊なのか何かに乗ってる。
It looks like a painting... is it between the legs, or a sheep, or something riding on it?
これ牛じゃない？
Isn't this a cow?
広い草原みたいなところで、黒い物体と白い物体がフュージョンしてる。
In a wide field, a black object and a white object are merging.
羊だよ、羊がお股に乗ってんじゃねえかな。
It's a sheep. A sheep riding a horse, I think.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
キーワードナンバー2は「る」です。
Keyword number 2 is 'ru'.
全く想像つかない。らでん後ろ向いてるから見れないんだけどさ。
I can't imagine it at all. Raden is facing away so I can't see.
もういいよ、ReGLOSS俺らアルバムで行こうぜ。
That's enough. ReGLOSS, let's go with 'album'.
よく分かんないけど、ぽいよね。
I don't really get it, but it seems like it.
キーワード1、ア！
Keyword 1: A!
キーワード2、ル！
Keyword 2: Ru!
キーワードナンバー3、バ！
Keyword number 3: Ba!
キーワードナンバー4、ム！
Keyword number 4: Mu!
せーの、
One, two...
アルバム！
ALBUM!
どや。
How's that?
これ、もう振り向いちゃいけないのかな、これは。
I wonder if we're not supposed to turn around yet.
まだじゃない？
Isn't it too early?
振り向け！
Turn around!
振り向いちゃえ！
Just turn around!
うわ！なんかある！
Whoa! There's something there!
うわ！何これ、何？
Whoa! What is this?
何これ、何これ？
What is this? What is this?
すごい、何これ？
Amazing, what is this?
じゃ、ちょっと宝箱に向かってさっきの呪文もう一回唱えるか。
Okay, let's face the treasure chest and say the spell again.
え、何だっけ？
Wait, what was it again?
アルバムね。
Album, right.
アルバムだよ。
It's album.
ごめん、ごめん。
Sorry, sorry.
行くよ。
Here we go.
せーの、
One, two...
アルバム！
ALBUM!
どうだ。
How about that?
わー！
Whoa!
脱出成功！
Escape successful!
やったー！
We did it!
こんな難しい問題、生でやらせんなよ。危ねー。
Don't make us solve such hard puzzles live. That was close!
解けないかと思ったわ。
I thought we were never going to solve it.
怖かったー。
That was scary.
何これ、この会場！
What's with this venue?!
なんかニューアニバーサリーって書いてある。
It says Happy Anniversary over there.
ねー。ハッピーアニバーサリーだね。
Yeah. It's Happy Anniversary.
ハッピーアニバーサリー。
Happy Anniversary.
ハッピー、ハッピー。
Happy, happy.
なんか、この配信前にスタッフさんが、いや簡単、すごい簡単だからとか言って。
You know, before the stream, the staff were like, "Oh, it's easy, it's really easy."
そう、言ってたの。めちゃくちゃ難しいじゃないか。
Right, they did. It was incredibly hard!
美術系って浮けてんのかと思って、びっくりしちゃった。
I thought they were going easy on us art majors, I was shocked.
怖かったー。
It was scary.
あのー、それぞれがちょっと得意っぽい分野の問題になってたのは良かったね。
Well, it was good that the questions were in areas we're each somewhat good at.
そうだね。
That's true.
知らねーよ。あたしやることなかった。
I didn't know any of it. I had nothing to do.
ビビッパで終わっちゃった。
I ended with just "Bibippa."
はい。ということで、皆さん、もうお分かりかと思いますけれども、
Okay. So, I think everyone already has an idea, but...
まずはこちらの映像をご覧ください。
...first, please take a look at this footage.
Snapshot / ReGLOSS 2nd Album
2025.11.12 ON SALE
うわー！ということでさっきの問題が難しかった話をみんなで笑いながら、
Whoa! So we were all laughing about how hard that puzzle was...
すみません、VTRの裏でちょっと話してました。すみません。
...sorry, we were talking during the VTR. Sorry!
すみません、すみません。
Sorry, sorry.
はい。ということでですね、なんとReGLOSSのセカンドアルバムが11月12日に発売決定！
Okay! So, believe it or not, ReGLOSS's 2nd album will be released on November 12th!
いぇーい！
Yay!
アルバムのタイトルは『Snapshot』。
The album title is "Snapshot."
パシャ、パシャ、パシャ。
*Click, click, click.*
スナップ写真のように、日々の暮らしに寄り添い、
Like a snapshot, it's an album that stays close to your daily life...
共に、時を重ねていけるような、そんなアルバムになっています。はい。
...and we hope it's something we can grow through time together with. Yes.
今回のアルバムはホロライブ公式ECサイト限定の完全生産限定盤と通常盤の二種類あります。
This album comes in two versions: a limited edition exclusive to the Hololive Official EC Site, and a regular edition.
完全生産限定盤は海外のおもちゃを彷彿とさせるブリスターパック仕様で、
The limited edition comes in a blister pack that's reminiscent of overseas toys,
CDの他に、アルバムの衣装と同じデニム風の色味が可愛いカメラ型小物入れケース、
and includes a cute camera-shaped pouch in a denim color matching the album's outfits,
ソロ曲のビジュアルを使用したソロシリーズカードセット、
a Solo Series Card Set using visuals from the recently released solo songs,
そして複製コメント入りランダムプロフィールカード一枚がランダムで付いてきますよ。
and it also comes with one random profile card with a printed comment.
通常盤は全国流通もします。
The regular edition will also be available nationwide.
初回プレス限定の封入特典としてランダムミニカードが一枚封入されています。
As a first-press bonus, it includes one random mini-card.
詳細はSNSや今後、随時発表される各販売店の情報をチェックしてください。
For details, please check our social media and info from each retailer as it's released.
ホロライブ公式ECサイトの予約はこの時間からスタート！
Pre-orders on the Hololive Official EC Site start now!
おおー！
Whoa!
予約ページのリンクが表示されていると思いますので、チェックしてください。
A link to the pre-order page should be displayed now, so please check it out.
Snapshot, Snapshot.
さらに店舗別特典のラインナップを公開しちゃいます！
Plus, we're revealing the lineup of retailer-specific bonuses!
絵柄など詳しい情報はまた後日公開予定です。
Detailed information about the designs will be released at a later date.
またこのアルバムに収録されている楽曲はデジタルでの配信も予定しておりますので、お楽しみに。
Also, the songs in this album are scheduled for digital release, so look forward to that.
よろしくお願いします。
We hope you enjoy it.
そしてセカンドアルバムのリリースを記念して、今年もリリースイベントの開催が決定しました！
And to celebrate the 2nd album's release, we've decided to hold a release event this year too!
いぇーい！
Yay!
期間内に対象商品をHMV&BOOKS onlineにて全額内金でご予約いただいた方の中から、
Those who pre-order eligible products with full payment at HMV&BOOKS online...
抽選でご当選された方をリリース記念イベントにご招待。
...will be entered into a draw to be invited to the commemoration event.
今回は第1部リリナデ、第2部ラデはじとなっております。
This time, Part 1 features Riri-Nade, and Part 2 features Rade-Haji.
応募待ってるよー！
We're looking forward to your applications!
待ってまーす！
We're waiting!
待って、ちょい待っちゃ。あたしたちライブ会場向かってる途中じゃなかったっけ？
Wait, hang on. Weren't we on our way to the live venue?
え、そうだったっけ？
Wait, really?
いや、違う。違う。ライブ会場行くってあっちだわ。
No, no. The way to the live venue is over that way.
そっか。
I see.
ということで、この後ですね、ミニライブ！
So, up next is a mini-live!
本日MVが公開された『Our Time Yellow』のパフォーマンスもあるんで、最後まで見てくださいね。
We'll perform "Our Time Yellow," which got an MV today, so watch till the end.
ねー。ライブ中でもまだ重大発表があるとかないとか。おら！おら！
Yeah. And there might even be more major announcements during the live. Hey! Hey!
まだまだ2周年記念配信は始まったばかり。ほな、急いでライブ会場にいらっしゃい！
The 2nd Anniversary celebration stream has only just begun. Well then, hurry over to the live venue!
行こうよ！
Let's go!
行こう行こう！
Let's go, let's go!
どういうステップ踏んでるの？
What kind of steps are you taking?
行こう！
Let's go!
どうした？これホントにライブ会場に繋がってるの？
What's wrong? Does this really lead to the live venue?
もう繋がるよ！
It's about to connect!
熱い熱い！
It's hot, it's hot!
真っ白だ！
It's pure white!
全然見えなかった！
I couldn't see anything at all!
行こう行こう行こう！
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
着替えようか
Shall we change?
着替えよう！
Let's change!
よいしょっと
Heave-ho
やばい、チャック引っかかっちゃった
Oh no, the zipper got stuck
え、大丈夫？
Wait, are you okay?
これ干してあげようか？
Should I hang this up to dry for you?
え！？ちょっと待って！
Eh!? Wait a second!
落ち着いて！
Calm down!
ジャージだから、また買ってもらおう、ジャージ
Since it's a jersey, let's have them buy us another one
そうだね
That's right
やばい、変な汗かきすぎて、もうなんか冷や汗という冷や汗が止まらなかったよ
Oh no, I sweated so weirdly, I just couldn't stop having cold sweats
難しかった？
Was it difficult?
やばい、なんか予想外だった。なんか謎解きみたいなのが出てくるのかなと思ってた
Oh no, it was kind of unexpected. I thought something like riddles would come up
普通に雑学というか知識系だったね。すごいびっくりした
It was just general knowledge or a trivia thing, wasn't it? I was really surprised
知識を初めにもちょめんなよ！
Don't look down on knowledge, okay?!
ジョーカー出てきた時だっけ？
Was it when the Joker came out?
でも青酸カリ、ちょっと答えられなかったの悔しいわ
But I'm frustrated that I couldn't answer about potassium cyanide
なんかアーモンドにこれは青酸カリって、最三見たことあるのにな。ありえって思って
Even though I've seen "this is potassium cyanide" for almonds many times before... I was like "unbelievable"
そうね、知ってるやつあんまないもんな
Yeah, not many people know that
そろそろか
Is it about time?
何歌う？
What are we singing?
今から決める感じ？
Are we deciding just now?
カラオケじゃないんだけど、何歌う？
It's not karaoke, but... what should we sing?
何歌う？何にしようかね
What are we singing? What should we go with?
踊りながら歌えるやつがいいんじゃない？
Wouldn't it be good to do something we can sing while dancing?
踊りながらってハードル高いこと言うね
Saying "while dancing" is setting the bar pretty high
LAKI MODE
作詞：OHTORA
Lyrics: OHTORA
作曲：OHTORA / cat biscuit
Music: OHTORA / cat biscuit
編曲：cat biscuit
Arrangement: cat biscuit
止めて煽いだ雲の上
Stop it, above the fanned clouds
目の端に包まれたの星待って
Wait for the stars wrapped in the corner of the eye
ねえ、空起きた光に跨って
Hey, riding on the light that just woke up in the sky
一緒に冬光交わそう
Let's exchange winter lights together
留守か無しの星たちが気気としてステップ刻んで
The stars, here or not, carve out steps as they please
わがもの顔でなびくアイソレーション暮れきめカプセデッド
Isolation fluttering with a self-important face, twilight-colored capsule...
冴えない夢にはおあいそ
To the dull dreams, a polite smile
花咲く笑顔に似合いそ
Suits the blooming smile
色なす全てのパレスを踊ろよ
Let's dance in all the colorful palaces
Under the starlight
流れに身を委ねて　ただ漂うだけのハートビート
Surrendering to the flow, a heartbeat that just drifts along
君だけのプレイリスト　Mind flow 耳元まで運ぶよ
A playlist just for you, Mind flow, I'll deliver it to your ears
ドンピシャなエモーション
A perfect emotion
ドンピシャなラキーモード
A perfect Laki Mode
闇を照らすオーロラ　言葉選ず踊り場
Aurora lighting up the darkness, a dance floor without the need for words
踊っていたいずっと　またとないこの日を
I want to keep dancing forever, this unique day
降り注ぐプラズマ　君がエレバプラスワン
Showering plasma, if you choose, plus one
色濃く写そう　ビビッドなハイライト
Let's project it vividly, vivid highlights
やみつきになれダンスダンス　ハイになるまでアイスアイス
Get addicted, dance dance, until you're high, ice ice
寝ても覚めても　華やぐトワイライト
Awake or asleep, the brilliant twilight
煌めいたらナイスナイス
If it sparkles, nice nice
もっと光合図アイスアイス
More, light signals, ice ice
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
次の曲は…！
The next song is...!
SUPER DUPER!
はじめとらでんバージョン feat. 尾丸ポルカ＆宝鐘マリン！
Hajime & Raden version feat. Omaru Polka & Houshou Marine!
行くぞー！
Let's go!
ざらついた胸の奥　愛してやまないもの　疑うことも知らないまま
Deep in my roughened heart, things I love endlessly, still without knowing how to doubt
そう　遂げる覚悟はできてるよ
Yes, I'm prepared to see it through to the end
ギミダ　ギミダビライナ
Give me the, give me the be right now
SUPER DUPER お口のシャングリラ　惹かれるまで踊ろうよ
SUPER DUPER, Shangri-La for the ears, let's dance until we're drawn in
誰が何と言おうと　気にしないリミッター解除
No matter what anyone says, I don't care, limiter released
想うだけの自由だけ
Only the freedom to think
美しい声を響かせて
Let those beautiful voices ring out
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, ah ah
俯いた世界を　変えてみせよう
Let's change this downcast world
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, SUPER DUPER
一喜一憂も
Joy and sorrow
一期一会も注いで
Pouring into once-in-a-lifetime encounters too
一進一退でいて
Stay in a state of ebb and flow
こよなく恋したメロディーと
With the melody I loved so dearly
会えなくて放したレプリカ
And the replica I let go because we couldn't meet
名もなき君との境界線を越え　リプレイ
Cross the boundary with nameless you, replay
SUPER DUPER お口のシャングリラ　惹かれるまで踊ろうよ
SUPER DUPER, Shangri-La for the ears, let's dance until we're drawn in
誰が何と言おうと　気にしないリミッター解除
No matter what anyone says, I don't care, limiter released
想うだけの自由だけ
Only the freedom to think
美しい声を響かせて
Let those beautiful voices ring out
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, ah ah
俯いた世界を　変えてみせよう
Let's change this downcast world
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, SUPER DUPER
ありがとう！
Thank you!
イェーイ！最高だよー！
Yay! That was awesome!
次の曲は…！
The next song is...!
この曲ってことは、盛り上がって行く準備はできてるよな！
Since it's this song, you're all ready to get pumped up, right!
イェーイ！
Yay!
行くよー！
Here we go!
OK! DOKI! 史上最高アレバイズ
OK! DOKI! The best ever Arise
EASY! BREEZY! 歌い鳴らせばフェイバリット
EASY! BREEZY! If you sing it out, it's a favorite
OK! DOKI! このままいたいダイアローグ
OK! DOKI! A dialogue that wants to stay like this
EASY! BREEZY! 踊ろうよ　Everybody
EASY! BREEZY! Let's dance, everybody
それぞれ異なった勝ち誇るマイナスをプラスになり待ち
Each different triumphant minus waiting to become a plus
笑えば不敵やって勝ち核算　お決まりのアイスタから始まる
If we laugh, it's a fearless win-loss calculation, starting from the usual eye star
愉快な仲間気づけば　バイマイサイ
Joyful friends, if I notice, they're by my side
もっと話したい時バカ騒ぎ
When I want to talk more, we have a blast
運命共同体　転生してゆく君のアイラック
Destined community, your eye-luck that reincarnates
分かち合えるエンパシー　共に迷チャンスは
Shared empathy, together the chance to get lost is...
Reach the top!
絶対絶対絶対絶対的煌めき中
Absolutely, absolutely, absolutely, absolute sparkling
今は自由気まま水色のユニバース
Now it's a carefree light blue universe
塗りつぶせ真っ白に　シンクロするシノプス
Paint it all white, synchronizing synops
限界突破　引きつける眼光
Break through the limits, eyes that draw you in
あれ？こんなところにカメラが！
Oh? There's a camera here!
今、自撮り中ー！
We're taking a selfie now!
OK! DOKI! 史上最高アレバイズ
OK! DOKI! The best ever Arise
Easy Breezy
歌い出せば Favorite
If we start singing, it's our favorite
OOKY DOKY
このままでいたいよね
We want to stay like this, right?
Easy Breezy
踊ろうよ Everybody
Let's dance, everybody
ひとしずくの Flavor
A drop of flavor
また一人も一緒に会いたくなる気持ち
The feeling of wanting to meet everyone together again
書き留めのモノローグ
The monologues I wrote down
繋がるプロローグ
The prologue that connects
走る時間 あっという間のストリーム
Running time, a stream in the blink of an eye
みんなといる空間がエクストリーム
The space with everyone is extreme
量産するかげがえのないメモリー
Irreplaceable memories being mass-produced
さらに結びつく Next Dream
Tying even closer to the Next Dream
運命
Destiny
響き合いたい
Want to resonate together
Dance Dance して
Doing Dance Dance
ゆく喜怒哀楽
Expressing all sorts of emotions
Whoo!
分かち合えるエンパシー
Empathy we can share
共に目指すは
What we aim for together is...
Reach to the top! Yay!
絶対 絶対 絶対的 Killer tune
Absolute, absolute, absolute killer tune
今は自由気ままに色づくユニバース
Now, the universe colors as it pleases
三者三様みんなシンクロするシナプス
In our own ways, everyone's synapses synchronize
限界突破 引きつけろミラクル
Break through the limits, pull in the miracle
OOKY DOKY 此処は最高 Everybody
OOKY DOKY, this place is the best, everybody
Easy Breezy 歌い出せば Favorite
Easy Breezy, if we start singing, it's our favorite
OOKY DOKY このままでいたいよね
OOKY DOKY, we want to stay like this, right?
Easy Breezy 踊ろうよ Everybody
Easy Breezy, let's dance, everybody
ということで！いつもの挨拶、大丈夫？息途切れてない？大丈夫？
And with that! Is the usual greeting okay? Not out of breath? Okay?
いつもの挨拶から行きますよ！
Let's start with our usual greeting!
Reach to the top,
We are ReGLOSS!
はい、ということで「Lucky Mode」と「Super Duper」、
Yes! And so, we performed "Lucky Mode" and "Super Duper",
そして「OOKY DOKY」の3曲を聴いていただきましたー！
and then "OOKY DOKY"—three songs in total!
バディーズです！
It's the buddies!
皆さん盛り上がってますかー！？
Is everyone hyped up!?
はい、ということで、えっと...あ！なんか今エックス・トレンドに入ったって！？
Yes! And so... oh! I heard we're trending on X now!?
えー！すごい！
Ehh! Amazing!
えっ、て、あのSNSですか！？やばい！
Wait, you mean *that* SNS!? No way!
あの有名な！？有名人の！？それじゃないだろ！
That famous one!? With the celebrities!? Not that one!
ねえ、たくさんポストしてくださってありがとうございます！引き続きよろしくお願いします！
Hey, thank you so much for all the posts! Please keep it up!
いやーでも久しぶりにさ、「Lucky Mode」と「Super Duper」なんか歌ったね。
Man, but it's been a while since we sang "Lucky Mode" and "Super Duper".
しかも今回こう...なんていうの、こういうミックスバージョンみたいなさ。
And this time it was... what do you call it, like a mixed version.
うんうん、スペシャルバージョン！
Yeah yeah, a special version!
「Super Duper」は久しぶり...あ、でもさ、一応一周年で一人で歌っていただいたんですけど。
It's been a while for "Super Duper"... oh, but well, you did sing it solo for the 1st anniversary.
そうだよね。そう、なんかちょっと久しぶりに聴けて嬉しくなっちゃったなー。
That's right. Yeah, I was happy to hear it after such a long time.
わかるー！一年ぶりぐらいか、確かに。
I know! It's been about a year, for sure.
最後のポーズなんだったの、みんな。これ。
What was that last pose, everyone? This one.
えー、最後ポーズやろうよ、今。せーの、はい！
Eh, let's do the last pose now. Ready, and... there!
なんだったと思う？当ててみてよ！え、社長、これマジで何！？
What do you think it was? Try to guess! Eh, Boss, what is this seriously!?
あ、あ、これはわかるでしょ！
Ah, ah, you know this one!
これは？鳴き声は？ピヨピヨ！ピヨピヨ！
This? What's the sound? Peep peep! Peep peep!
いや、コケコッコーでしょ！いやいや、それは鶏でしょ！
No, it's Cock-a-doodle-doo! No no, that's a chicken!
あ、でもひよこちゃんだしね。じゃあ、こちらは？これは分かりやすいんじゃない？
Ah, but she is a chick. Then, this one? Isn't this easy to understand?
鳴き声は？ぴょんぴょん！ぴょんぴょん！
The sound? Boing boing! Boing boing!
本当か？ペンギンって鳴くかな？
Really? Do penguins make that sound?
あ、でもペンギンって言ってる！すごい！じゃあ、らでちゃんも！
Ah, but they're saying penguin! Amazing! Then, Raden-chan too!
激しめの猫ちゃん。可愛いですね。はい、なんと最後はね、みんなでそれぞれの動物を表現しておりました！
A fierce kitty. So cute. Yes, for the end, we were all expressing our respective animals!
じゃあ、ちょっとここで一つ、嬉しいお知らせがあります！
Now then, we have one happy announcement to share!
な、なんと、コナミさんの BEMANI とのコラボが決定しましたー！
A... amazingly, a collaboration with KONAMI's BEMANI has been decided!
はい、こちらなんと！書き下ろしの！ここ重要ですよ、書き下ろしのコラボ楽曲や、
Yes! This is... amazingly! A newly written! This is important, a newly written collaboration song,
コナミオリジナル楽曲のカバーバージョンが BEMANI 機種に登場します！詳細は BEMANI ファンサイト、公式エックスをチェックしてください！
and cover versions of KONAMI original songs will appear on BEMANI machines! Check the official BEMANI site/X!
ねー、色々歌ったよね、このコラボに際してさ。
Right, we sang a lot for this collaboration.
本当におしゃれでいい感じの楽曲をね、リグロスで歌わせていただいたんですよ。ありがとうございます。
We really got to sing some stylish and nice songs as ReGLOSS. Thank you.
ぜひプレイして聴いてみてほしいです！
We really want you to play and listen to them!
ソロでもさ、ユニットとしても歌ったよね。
We sang them solo and as a unit too, right?
ランウェイ終わったな。
After the runway, huh?
ねえ、本当に。
Yeah, really.
色々色々聞けると思うので、楽しみにしていいてください！
I think we'll hear all sorts of things, so please look forward to it!
はーい！
Yeah!
はい、皆さん息は大丈夫そうですか？
Okay, everyone, is your breathing okay?
ですか？
Okay?
ギリギリ？ギリギリ！
Barely? Barely!
もっと喋る？
You're gonna talk more?
ギリ大丈夫。でもいけそう。
Barely okay, but I think I can do it.
いけそう？
You think so?
うん。
Yeah.
はい、ということでね、じゃあ皆、まだまだ！
Alright then, well, everyone, it's not over yet!
まだまだ終わりませんよ！まだまだ何かあるかもしれないですよ！
It's not over yet! There might be something more!
はい！はい！
Yes! Yes!
はい、ハッシュタグ、これもお願いします！
Also, please use the hashtag!
いっぱい呟いてください！ReGLOSS 2周年！
Please post a lot! ReGLOSS 2nd Anniversary!
はい、じゃあ次の曲、いいですか？
Okay, then, are you ready for the next song?
うん。
Yeah.
次の楽曲は、なんと！本日公開されたばかりの...
The next track is... what do you know, the song that was just released today!
あの曲！
That song!
うわー！
Whoa!
じゃあ、立ち位置に付きますか。
Well, shall we take our positions?
はい！はい！
Yes! Yes!
スン、スン、スン...
Sun, sun, sun...
何の曲かなー。
I wonder what song it is.
それでは聞いてください。『アワータイムイエロー』。
Well then, please listen to it. "Our Time Yellow".
空を仰ぎ挑む人生ゲーム
Life game facing the sky overhead
言い訳めいたハートに従って
Following the heart I decided to clear
現実は薄荷空プロットです
Reality is a peppermint sky plot
取り憑かれるお隣の芝生は愛
The grass is always greener on the other side
夕立ちちょっと切なあの娘は待て
That girl at dusk is impatient
二度と被った猫は剥がせない
I'll never reveal the mask I put on
痛みを識ってしまったマジシャン
A magician who has come to know pain
手の内はまだ明かせない
I can't reveal the trick yet
Yellow Yellow 0からループ
Yellow Yellow, loop from zero
点滅するピリオド
The period that blinks
Yellow Yellow 染まる紅い結晶
Yellow Yellow, the red crystal that stains
Our time, can't make over night
答え合わせの月見に
The moon that matches the answer
放なされても
Even if I'm released
No worries 私には私が付いてる
No worries, for me, I have me
酔いが醒めるまで
Until the intoxication subsides
あと少しだけ
Just a little more
真の愛捕らえる残像
The afterimage of catching the true love
Show step then we win the race
次の季節を越え
Beyond the next season
Bloom me Bloom me
どうかこの音を止めないで
Please don't stop this sound
Our Time Yellow Yellow
Ready for ready for Let's stay gold
Ready for ready for
Let's enjoy the moment
Look into the mirror
絡まってる蜘蛛のイエロー
The entangled yellow of spider webs
It happens all the time
踊らされたって構わない
I don't care if I'm played
予感に憑いて
Stuck in the obsession
時を宛てがって呉れて
Open up the time and let it go
Always be honest
永遠に変わらないもの
Things that won't change forever
Yellow Yellow 手をとり合えば
Yellow Yellow, if we join hands
そこに理由は要らない
No reasons are needed there
Yellow Yellow 染まる紅い結晶
Yellow Yellow, the red crystal that stains
As I wish you better better
いくつになっても 100点です
No matter how old I get, it's 100 points
希望 夢は人並みです
Hope and dreams are common
満ちる好きな運命は
A destiny like drifting through
人生ごと受け入れる
Accepting life as a whole
新機軸に脱皮 out of the box
To a new innovation, out of the box
右向いて左向いてポーズ、動いて go
Looking right, looking left, pose, move and go
大好き 24/7
Love it, 24/7
終着点は Eden or Heaven
Destination is Eden or Heaven
No time to waste 今だけを信じて
No time to waste, believe in now
セカンドフィナーレまで共に進め
Until the second finale, move forward together
酔いが醒めるまで
Until the intoxication subsides
あと少しだけ
Just a little more
真の愛捕らえる残像
The afterimage of catching the true love
Show step then we win the race
次の季節を越え
Beyond the next season
Boom me Boom me
乗せてこの音を止めないで
Please don't stop this sound
Our Time Yellow Yellow
Ready for ready for Let's stay gold
Ready for ready for
Let's enjoy the moment
一振りのダンス、一瞬の視線、一拍の鼓動
A single dance move, a momentary glance, a single beat of the heart.
一秒一秒が永遠に鳴り響く
Every single second resonates for eternity.
ReGLOSSが描いていく“今”を切り取った
A sequence of snapshots capturing the "now"...
一枚一枚の連続
...that ReGLOSS is painting.
そのすべてが連なり
It all connects...
観る人の記憶に焼きついていく
...and burns into the memories of those who watch.
2025.12.16 Tue.
Flashpoint ReGLOSS 1st Live
ARIAKE ARENA
それぞれの光が響き合い
Each person's light resonates...
世界をかたちづくる
...and shapes the world.
ReGLOSSはその瞬間を
ReGLOSS conveys that moment...
音楽とダンスで伝える
...through music and dance.
はい！ということで、みんな見た？見た？見た？
Alright! So, did everyone see it? Did you see? Did you see?
やばい！１２月１６日、有明アリーナにて…
Oh my god! On December 16th, at Ariake Arena...
もう一回…ティクス、ティクス、ティクス、ティクス、ティクス！
One more time... ticks, ticks, ticks, ticks, ticks!
１２月１６日、有明アリーナにて…
On December 16th, at Ariake Arena...
ReGLOSS 1st Live「Flashpoint」の開催が決定しましたー！
ReGLOSS 1st Live "Flashpoint" has been confirmed!
すごい！すごい！すごい！すごい！すごい！すごい！
Amazing! Amazing! Amazing! Amazing! Amazing! Amazing!
え、現地ライブってことだよね？
Wait, that means it's an in-person live concert, right?
そうだよ！
That's right!
そうだよね！
It is!
しかもめちゃくちゃデカい会場…
And it's a huge venue...
夢が叶うってこと…！
It means a dream is coming true...!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you everyone!
応援してくれたみんなのおかげだね。
It's all thanks to everyone who supported us.
１個目の夢が叶うかもしれないんだ。
One of our dreams might be coming true.
頑張ろう！
Let's do our best!
はい、でこちらのライブなんですけれども…
Yes, and regarding this live concert...
2ndアルバムで描いた世界観に連動して、ReGLOSSの「今」を記憶に焼き付ける、というテーマになっています。
Linked to the worldview of our 2nd album, the theme is "searing ReGLOSS's 'now' into memory."
つまり、まさに今の私たちの…
In other words, it's a concert that will be our...
…集大成となるライブでございます！
...culmination of everything we are right now!
そしてね、ライブのキービジュアルも改めてお見せしちゃいます！こちらデン！
And now, we're going to show you the key visual for the concert! Here it is!
このキービジュアルはね、ライブのテーマに合わせて…
This key visual was designed according to the theme of the concert...
ライブパフォーマンス中のReGLOSSを切り取ったイメージのデザインとなっています。
...and features a design inspired by snapshots of ReGLOSS mid-performance.
素敵！
Wonderful!
なんかまた普段のReGLOSSとは違った一面な感じがしたね。
It feels like another side of ReGLOSS, different from our usual selves.
今回のライブのハッシュタグは、#ReGLOSS_1stLive です！
The hashtag for this concert is #ReGLOSS_1stLive!
いっぱいポストしてみんなと盛り上がりまちょ！
Post a lot and let's get hyped with everyone!
お願いします！
Please join us!
まあ、さて、さて、そんな中みんなが気になっているであろう…
Now then, moving on to something everyone is likely curious about...
チケット情報をね、ちょっとみんなにお見せしようかなと思います。
I'd like to share the ticket information with you all.
チケット情報はこちらデン！デデーン！
The ticket information is right here! Ta-da!
TICKET チケット
現地会場
S席(Front Arena and Front Stand) 12,000円
A席(Rear Arena and Side Stand) 9,500円
B席(Rear Stand) 8,300円
配信 SPWN・ZAIKO 6,500円
TICKET
Venue Tickets
S-seat (Front Arena and Front Stand) 12,000 Yen
A-seat (Rear Arena and Side Stand) 9,500 Yen
B-seat (Rear Stand) 8,300 Yen
Streaming SPWN/ZAIKO 6,500 Yen
はい、チケットはS席、A席、B席の３種類です。
Yes, there are three types of tickets: S-seats, A-seats, and B-seats.
１次先行はこのあと２１時、このあと２１時からスタートです。
The first pre-sale starts tonight at 9 PM.
先着ではございません。抽選でございます。焦らずに申し込んでください。
It's not first-come-first-served. It's a lottery system. So please apply calmly.
さらに、会場には行けないよ、という人のために…
Also, for those who can't make it to the venue...
配信チケットもご用意しました。
Streaming tickets are also available.
こちらもこのあと２１時から販売開始です。
Sales for these also begin tonight at 9 PM.
続いて、会場のエリアマップはこちらデン！ジャン！
Next, here is the venue's area map! Ta-da!
ARIAKE ARENA SEAT MAP 座席表
S席(Front Arena and Front Stand)
A席(Rear Arena and Side Stand)
B席(Rear Stand)
ARIAKE ARENA SEAT MAP
S-seat (Front Arena and Front Stand)
A-seat (Rear Arena and Side Stand)
B-seat (Rear Stand)
はい、S席、A席、B席がそれぞれどこになるのかはこちらをチェックしてください。
Please check this to see where the S, A, and B seats are located.
エリアマップはこのあとホロライブ公式Xでもポストするんで、詳しくはね、そちらをご確認ください。
The area map will also be posted on the official Hololive X account, so please check there for details.
そしてみんな喜べ！トレンド１位！
And everyone, celebrate! We're #1 on trending!
そしてそして、ライブのグッズについては１０月１０日のReGLOSS公式YouTubeチャンネルにて発表します！
And regarding the concert goods, we'll announce them on the official ReGLOSS YouTube channel on October 10th!
Flashpoint ReGLOSS 1st Live
10.10 FRI.
ライブグッズ販売決定！
ReGLOSS公式YouTubeチャンネルにて公開！
Flashpoint ReGLOSS 1st Live
Friday, October 10th
Concert goods confirmed for sale!
Reveal on the official ReGLOSS YouTube channel!
素敵なグッズがいっぱいあるので見逃さないでね。
There are lots of great items, so don't miss it.
そしてそして、今回発表したライブの情報や次回のグッズの情報は特設サイトにて掲載いたします！
Also, information about the live concert announced today and the upcoming goods will be posted on the special website!
うちらちょっと事前に見たよね？
We saw it a little beforehand, didn't we?
見た見た！
We did!
特設サイト、お手洗い行ってたかもしれない。
For the special site, I might have been in the restroom.
はい、すごいかっこいいサイトなんで是非とも覗いてみてください。
Yes, it's a very cool site, so please take a look.
特設サイトは、えっと、「ReGLOSS 1st Live」検索お願いします。
For the special site, please search for "ReGLOSS 1st Live."
今後も追加情報を更新していくのでブックマークとチェックよろしくお願いします！
We'll keep updating it with more info, so please bookmark and check it!
現地ですって。やばいね。
An in-person live. Incredible, right?
どうよみんな？
How are you all feeling?
はい！もうリリカはこれもうずっとデビューの時から言ってるんだけど…
Yes! I've been saying this ever since our debut, but...
もうダンスも歌もどちらもやっぱり自信もなかったし得意じゃないって思ってたリリカが…
I had no confidence in my dancing or singing and didn't think I was good at either...
ちょっとずつなんかそれぞれを好きになっていけていて…
But little by little, I've come to love both...
でみんなにちゃんとその成長した姿を見てもらいたいって思ってて…
And I really want to show everyone how much I've grown...
そう、その夢が今回のまたね新しい現地ライブという場で叶うのかもしれないなと思ったらめちゃくちゃ嬉しいです！
Thinking that this dream might come true at this new in-person live venue makes me so happy!
えっと、奏はなんか正直まだ実感がわいてなくて...
Um, honestly, for Kanade, it hasn't really sunk in yet...
現地ライブ...本当に？本当に？みたいな...
A live concert... Is it for real? For real? That's how I feel...
なんか実感が本当にわかなくて。
It just really hasn't sunk in for me.
でも、なんかずっとさ、現地ライブしたいしたいって言ってきて、
But, you know, I've been saying I want to do a live concert forever,
いざ決定ってなって、世に出ると、なんか本当に不思議な気持ち。
so now that it's decided and announced, it feels really strange.
めちゃくちゃ嬉しいんだけどね！なんか夢のようで、
I'm incredibly happy! But it's like a dream,
逆に何にも感じないような...
that I almost feel nothing at all...
実感がまだないんだよね、そうそう。
It hasn't sunk in yet, right. Exactly.
じわじわと後から、うわー嬉しいってなると思うんだけど...
I think it'll hit me later, like "Wow, I'm so happy"...
おめでた！ありがとう！
Congratulations! Thank you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
みんなのおかげです。
It's all thanks to everyone.
番長はどう？
How about you, Bancho?
いや同じくね、実感がわかなくて、
Well, same here, it hasn't sunk in,
ちょ、本当なんだと。夢見心地でよくわからないけど。
like, wait, is this real? It feels like a dream and I don't quite get it.
でも、もうあと3ヶ月くらいしたら、GLOSSerのみんなが目の前にいて、
But in about three months, all the GLOSSers will be right there in front of us,
ハジメマシテパフォーマンスして、
and we'll do our first performance,
みんなが目の前で「キャー！」って言ってくれるってことでしょ？
and everyone will be screaming "Kyaa!" right in front of us, right?
キャー！
Kyaa!
って思ったら、もうすっごい嬉しいですよ。本当にありがとうございます。
Thinking about that, I'm just so happy. Thank you so much.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
嬉しいね。そして、らでんちゃんは？
It's great. And what about Raden-chan?
はい。現地ライブってことで、12月、少し早めの
Yes. Since it's a live concert in December, as a slightly early
ReGLOSSからのクリスマスプレゼントってことで、現地ライブさせていただくんですけれども。
Christmas present from ReGLOSS, we'll be holding a live concert.
まさか、まさか、まさかの現地ライブで。
I never, ever, ever expected a live concert.
本当にこんなありがたい機会が、生きててなかなかないじゃない？
Such a wonderful opportunity doesn't come often in life, does it?
ないよね、ないよね。
It really doesn't, it really doesn't.
そう。だから、すごくありがたいなと思うし、嬉しいなと思いますし。
Yeah. So I feel really grateful and happy about it.
今ね、絶賛レッスンでね、ライブに向けて我々頑張っておりますので、
Right now, we're in the middle of lessons and working hard for the concert,
ぜひ今後も応援してくれるととっても嬉しいです！
so we'd be very happy if you continue to support us!
皆さん本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you all so much!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
ねー、本当にライブ嬉しいね。
Man, I'm really happy about the concert.
最高だね！
It's the best!
でもその、ライブのためってわけでもないけどさ、いろんな楽曲を歌わせていただいていて、
But, it's not just for the live, we've been singing various songs,
今回「Our Time Yellow」も新しくリリースさせていただいたわけなんですけれども。
and this time we've newly released "Our Time Yellow".
ちょっとその感想も話しちゃおうか、ここでね、せっかくの機会だから。
Let's talk a bit about our thoughts on it here, since we have the chance.
じゃあ逆順で行く？らでんちゃんどう？
Shall we go in reverse order? Raden-chan, how about you?
らでんはね、MV出たじゃん？MV出たから、
For Raden, the MV came out, right? Since it's out,
MVもね、もういろんなものが素敵なんだけど、中でもらでんは歌詞がすっごい好きなんで。
everything in the MV is wonderful, but Raden especially loves the lyrics.
ちょっとMVで見て「あ、いい曲だな」とか、
If you watched the MV and thought "Oh, it's a good song" or
MVすごいあの、めちゃめちゃ動いていいなって思った方は、
"The MV moves so much, it's great," then
もう一回次はね、歌詞に注目してくれるとすごく嬉しいな、なんて思います。
I'd be really happy if you could focus on the lyrics next time.
おー、いいですね。
Oh, that's good.
番長は？
How about you, Bancho?
いやもうとにかく、リズムとメロディが大好きだしな。
Well, anyway, I really love the rhythm and melody.
ズクズクズクズク...
Zuku-zuku-zuku-zuku...
全部疾走感があって、なんかこう、そののってる言葉のメロディも全部なんか、
It all has a sense of speed, and the melody of the lyrics,
ビートもよかったり、なんかこう、テューン、テューンって言ったり、
the beat is good, it goes "tune, tune",
なんかこう激しいやん、移り変わりが。秋の予兆というかさ。
it's intense, you know, the transitions. Like a sign of autumn.
なんかもうすっごいメロディ大好きです。
I just really love the melody.
いっぱい聞いてください。奏は？
Please listen to it a lot. Kanade?
奏はまず曲がものすごく大好きだし、
First of all, Kanade really loves the song, and
今日みんなとさ、初めてMVを見たじゃないですか。
we watched the MV together for the first time today, right?
MVを見ると、なんかすごいかっこいい感じになっていて、なんか大感激でした。
Watching the MV, it looked so cool, I was deeply moved.
個人的に、奏が一番好きなMVシーンは、
Personally, Kanade's favorite scene in the MV is
こういうシーン。
this kind of scene.
どこだろう？どこだろう？
Where is it? Where is it?
らでんの所だ、らでんの所。1番の終わりだよ、1番の終わり。
It's Raden's part. At the end of the first verse, the first verse.
サビの終わり。フリーズザモーメントの所だよ。
At the end of the chorus. The "Freeze the moment" part.
あそこ、プニョンってやってた。
I was doing a "punyon" there.
この日のために、奏頑張りました。
Kanade worked hard for this day.
さらっとね。
So smooth.
リリカちゃんは？
How about Ririka-chan?
リリカもね、やっぱり「Our Time Yellow」はすごく元気になれる曲じゃない？
For Ririka too, "Our Time Yellow" is a song that really cheers you up, isn't it?
テンション上げ上げってなる曲で、すごい聞いてて楽しいし、
It's a song that gets your energy up, it's so fun to listen to, and
あと踊ってても...
also while dancing...
（激しく動く音）すごいね、いっぱい激しいところが大好きです。
(Intense movement sounds) It's great, I love all the intense parts.
「多分そんなに心配しなかったです！」
"Maybe I didn't worry that much!"
多分ね。大丈夫。聞いてください。
Probably. It's okay. Please listen to it.
え、このサビのさ、これめっちゃかっこよくない？ここ。
Hey, this part of the chorus, isn't it super cool? Right here.
（興奮したリアクション）
(Excited reactions)
ここ好きなんだよね。
I really like this part.
わかるわかる。
I totally get it.
まあね、ちょっと引き続き私たちは、アルバムに収録される新曲の練習なんかもね、
Well, we're continuing to work very hard on practicing
めちゃくちゃ頑張ってますので、ライブ楽しみにしていてくれたら嬉しいです！
the new songs for the album, so we'd be happy if you look forward to the live!
それじゃあ、最後の曲行きましょうか。
Well then, let's move on to the final song.
最後ですか。いける？
The last one? Ready?
お水飲んで、大丈夫？
Drink some water, you okay?
水飲んだか？
Did you drink water?
水飲んだかな？
みんな何の曲だと思うー？
What song do you all think it is?
えー何歌おうかなー？
Hmm, what should we sing?
えー、何歌おうかなー？
Eh, what should we sing?
ReGLOSSの曲だったら、やっぱ最後は瞬間ハートビートじゃない？
If it's a ReGLOSS song, surely the last one should be Instant Heartbeat?
シンメトリーもあるんじゃない？
Maybe Symmetry too?
フィーリングラデーションとかもあるし。
There's also Feeling Gradation and such.
じゃ、ちょっと水飲んでくるわ。
Well then, I'm going to drink some water.
いってらっしゃーい。
See you!
ヤケドだね、ヤケドもそうだし。
It's Genchi, and Genchi was also performed.
泡沫色も出ましたし。
And Bubble Time Color too.
立ち位置つきましょうか？
Shall we take our positions?
行きましょうか、つきましょうか。
Let's go, let's take them.
お、こっちということは...
Oh, being over here means...
わかる人多分あんまりいないかも。
There probably aren't many who'd understand.
うちらだけだと思う。
I think it's just us.
立ち位置がここ、ということは、みたいな。
Our positions being here means...
それでは、聴いてください。
And now, please listen.
ミッドサマートラス。
Midsummer Terrace.
今日は2周年だから、手拍子もっとしたい！
It's our 2nd anniversary today, so I want to hear more clapping!
いくぞー！
Here we go!
焼け付くような日差し
The burning rays of the sun
水面に浮かぶスパンコール
Spangles floating on the water's surface
発色夏色と逆光の裏側で
With vibrant summer colors and behind the backlight
あの日の青春を呼び起こしてる
Recalling the youth of that day
目に映る走馬灯をくぐって
Passing through the revolving lantern in my eyes
裸足で走ってる砂の上
Running barefoot on the sand
ガラスの淵で回りまわる輝く瑠璃色のビー玉
The shining lapis-colored marble spinning on the glass edge
なんだかその笑顔、ホント紙一重だ
Somehow that smile is truly paper-thin
フィルムを覗けばノンフィクション
Peering through the film, it's non-fiction
彩に解されたメモリー
Memories unraveled into colors
リセットなんてできないから
Because you can't just reset it
Love yourself, just as you are now.
踊ってみたサマー
Tried dancing summer
アルゴリズムの中で
Within the algorithm
最速でダイビングして
Diving at top speed
切り取ってきたアイラ
The island I cut out
これがきっと愛だ
This is surely love
二度とは忘れないように
So I'll never forget it again
レモン、ライム、オレンジ、君と一生分の思い出
Lemon, lime, orange, a lifetime of memories with you
何気ない一日が One of a kind.
A casual day is one of a kind.
あっち向いてホイ！
Look that way!
えい！あっちだー！
Ei! Over there!
いえーい！
Yay!
氷が溶けては渦巻いた魔法の杖代わりのマドラー
The ice melted and swirled, the stirrer acting as a magic wand
喉をくぐり抜けた爽やか柑橘系のフレーバー
The refreshing citrus flavor passing down my throat
爽やかな気流に乗って
Riding on the refreshing air current
波の返りを見守ってるビーチサイド
Watching the waves return on the beachside
あどけない面影に焦がれ
Yearning for the innocent features
微かに触れそうな指先
Fingertips that almost seem to touch
きらめいて上塗りしてしまうわ
It sparkles and I end up painting over it
Get ahead, what you used to be.
踊ってみたサマー
Tried dancing summer
アルゴリズムの中で
Within the algorithm
最速でダイビングして
Diving at top speed
切り取ってきたアイラ
The island I cut out
これがきっと愛だ
This is surely love
二度とは忘れないように
So I'll never forget it again
ミッドサマートラス、オーイエス！
Midsummer Terrace, oh yes!
It's time to wake up, get up, OK!
見ているだけでフェイバリット、そんな心はまだ実り
A favorite just by looking, that heart is still ripening
寝起きの太陽も願ってもない散々日和
Even the morning sun is a perfect, brilliant day
白飛びせず持ったまばゆいのは...
Holding onto the dazzling light without overexposure...
ReGLOSSのせい！
Is because of ReGLOSS!
踊ってみたサマー
Tried dancing summer
アルゴリズムの中で
Within the algorithm
最速でダイビングして
Diving at top speed
切り取ってきたアイラ
The island I cut out
これがきっと愛だ
This is surely love
二度とは忘れないように
So I'll never forget it again
レモン、ライム、オレンジ、君と一生分の思い出
Lemon, lime, orange, a lifetime of memories with you
何気ない一日が One of a kind.
A casual day is one of a kind.
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
12月16日、みんなと会えるの楽しみにしてるよー！
I'm looking forward to seeing everyone on December 16th!
有明アリーナも配信も、全力で盛り上げます！
We'll give our all at Ariake Arena and on the stream!
これからもお楽しみに！
Please look forward to it!
セカンドアルバムもたくさん聴いてください！
Please listen to our second album a lot!
ということで！
And so!
せーの！
One, two!
ReGLOSSでした！
We were ReGLOSS!
またねー！
See you later!
現地でお会いしましょう！
See you at the venue!
みんな会おうね！
Let's all meet!
最高のライブにする！
We'll make it the best live!
現地ライブたのしみだ！
I'm looking forward to the live on-site!
ReGLOSSに会いに来てね！
Come see ReGLOSS!
フロアを沸かせるよ！
We're going to hype up the floor!